in your play today or was it just your
play today?
>> Not at all.
[snorts]
>> Three years now of missing the playoffs.
Typically that results in change for
most NFL organizations. Do you still
have confidence in the people in the
front office and the coaching staff that
they can get this roster in a place and
and this team in a place where that
wouldn't happen next year?
>> A lot of confidence.
>> Why?
>> Because I know how hard people work at
it. We got the right people. uh
>> starts with players playing better and
today it was me.
>> From the outside, Joe, a lot of fans are
going to disagree. They're going to say
that the organization top to bottom,
front office doesn't have enough people
or the right people in place. You
honestly feel that they do and why?
>> This is a team effort.
You know, at the end of the day, players
got to play better on the field.
>> Today, today was me.
>> I got to be better.
>> What do you feel like you could have
done better today? everything.
>> Why was Why was it so tough out there?
What were they doing that made such a
challenge? [snorts]
>> They're getting good pressure. Um but
you know, some
uncharacter uncharacteristic mental
mistakes on on my end and some unforced
errors.
>> Does that you touch on the mindset
talking? Do you think those things could
be intertwined at all as to maybe why
didn't go the way you wanted to?
>> No.
>> Early on. Can you take us through
the you had a throw to Jamar. It was
right before the interception. Throw to
Jamar in the end zone and the
interception where it was a tad high.
Just those two those two plays. It just
felt like you guys were just tad off.
>> Yeah, on the go. I felt good about where
I put it. He got tugged a little bit.
Um, you know, sometimes you get those
calls, sometimes you don't. But
I felt good about where I put that one.
And then, yeah, obviously the
interception was was a bit high. What
were you thinking as you go back on the
field for the last time in conditions
you probably would not have? What was
running through your mind as you go back
after the pick six? [snorts]
>> I mean at that point it was over. So
just protect yourself.
>> Joe, out of playoff contention, do you
want to play the last three games?
Personally,
>> I do. [snorts]
>> Joe, today it was the offense. Other
games it's been the defense. Why has
complimentary football been so hard for
this team to find this year?
>> We haven't been a good football team.
you know, bad football bad football
teams
do losing things. And uh,
you know, if you're if you're wanting to
compete for championships and be in the
playoffs, then
number one, your quarterback has to play
better than they than I did today.
>> How far does that gap feel right now,
Joe, between this team and what's
expected of a championship level?
>> Not that far. Not that far.
>> Is this the worst you felt after loss?
probably
>> and lo losing losing socks. Losing
socks.
>> I know you're taking a lot of
responsibility for today's game, but one
of the main things that has come out of
this season is how much is on your plate
and and the record when you were out
when you were out and last week's
perfect example, the turnovers, you guys
lose the game. Do you feel like there's
too much weight on you where it feels
like if you're not perfect, the team is
good enough around you to pick you up?
>> You know, I want everything on my plate.
I want um that's the position I want to
be in. And you know, I feel confident in
all those guys in the locker room. Like
I said today,
nobody there's not a team in the NFL
that would have won the game today if if
I was a quarterback.
>> Teams team's record is headed in the
wrong direction. Do you think your play
is slipping down the slope in the wrong
direction over the last couple years?
>> No, I feel very confident in how I've
played. Obviously today, in my opinion,
is an outlier. I think I've been
consistently great for
um years and years and years.
>> Did they change up that pressure at all
from Thanksgiving? Did they do anything
different that way
on Thanksgiving?
>> Uh I'd say they blitz they blitzed less.
Um their front four was able to get a
little more pressure. Uh so credit to
them.
>> What kind of on that first sack the uh
the 15 yard on the third down going
their end. What kind of happened there?
Uh that
>> mental mistake by me.
>> Yeah. Is it the same thing on the uh the
pick six? Is that kind of It looked like
it was a similar pressure that they had
on the gap. Was that the same or no?
>> Um I'll have to see the film on that
one. Uh we'll see
>> what this is the hardest I think you've
ever been on yourself after a game. Why?
>> Even I think this is one of the worst
games that I've I've played. Um,
you know, I'm honest with myself and my
play and I hold myself to a high
standard and
today didn't come close.
>> Joe, with playoffs off the table as a
competitor, how tough will it be now to
to to reindset and kind of get yourself
back into, you know, wanting to win
again, even even if
>> Not very tough.
>> You you mentioned the the mental mistake
on the the sack when you guys the first
drive of the game. Was that a pre- snap?
I made the wrong call.
Thanks.
>> Thanks. Thank you.